awayn.com 2019-06-26

# AWAYN - An Insider's Guide to 100K+ Local Adventures

#### **Last updated: MAY 22, 2018**

awayn ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://awayn.com/ website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.awayn.com/

#### **Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, other information ("Personal Information"). We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services.

You may choose to participate in Awayn community by providing content on the Website and Mobile Apps including but not limited to locations, stories, adventures, photos, reviews, lists, bookmarks, likes and follows.

If you provide information on behalf of someone else (or someone else provides information on your behalf), the person providing the information must have consent to do so from the person whose information is being provided. “Information” means information that can be used to distinguish or trace your identity, either alone or when combined with other information that is linked or linkable to you. Certain parts of the Services may be offered in conjunction with another company. If you provide information in such cases, both Awayn nd the other company(ies) may receive the information collected and use the information according to each company’s respective privacy policy and agreement with you.

#### **Log Data**

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

#### **Social Media Features**

Both Awayn Website and Mobile Apps include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook & Twitter Like button and Widgets. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Awayn Website and Mobile Apps. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them. 

#### **Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

#### **DoubleClick Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/

#### **Do Not Track Disclosure**

Awayn supports Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

#### **Store and process your data**

Awayn is committed to continuously protecting your information and protect your data from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. Some of the actions and safety measures taken by the Company to protect you include: • Using encryption to keep your data private; • Reviewing its information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures; • Restricting access to the data to Awayn employees, contractors and agents who need that information in order to process it. Everyone with access is subject to strict confidentiality obligations and will be disciplined or terminated if they do not comply with these obligations.

#### **Managing, Reviewing and Updating Your Data.  **

Awayn always strives to ensure your data is accurate. In the event you become aware of an error or inaccuracy in your data, you may notify Awayn at the email and/or address provided below. You have the right to access your data at any time in order to receive information on how your data is being used and for what purpose. 

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

#### **Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

#### **Compliance With Laws**

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

#### **Exporting, Removing and Deleting Your Data**

You have the right to export a copy of your data if you want to back it up or use it for another service. You also have the right to delete all or any portion of your data by contacting the Company at the address provided below. In some cases, the Company may retain data for a limited period when it is needed for a legitimate business or legal purpose. You will find the ability to export your data and delete your account within Settings on the Website and Mobile Apps.

#### **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

#### **International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### **Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

##### **Children's Privacy**

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 16 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 16. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 16 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

#### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 22nd, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

#### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

**Address:**

P.D.R.VC LLC 

427 N Tatnall St #92059   
Wilmington,  
Delaware 19801-2230
